serversmtp.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | smtp mail server

### Introduction

 **(a) Application of this Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement applies to the website http://www.turbo-smtp.com, https://turbo-smtp.com (the "Site"), which is owned and operated by turboSMTP Corp., carrying on business as turboSMTP ("turboSMTP").

 **(b) Your Consent**

By using the Site, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Statement and consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth herein.

 **(c) A Special Note About Children**

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may use this Site only in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

 **(d) Personal Information**

"Personal information" is information that can identify you as an individual and includes information such as your name, e-mail and billing address, your credit card number and expiry date. Information may cease to be “personal information” when it is stripped of all identifiers or aggregated with personal information collected from other individuals.

 **(e) Changes to the Statement**

The Statement may be changed periodically. By using the Site, you acknowledge our right to change the Statement. Any changes will be posted on the Privacy Statement page of the Site. We recommend that you visit the Privacy Statement page whenever you visit the Site to ensure you are aware of the current Statement.

### Our Commitment

turboSMTP respects, and is committed to protecting, your privacy. The goal of the Statement is to explain how we protect your privacy.

### Accountability

The Privacy Officer is responsible for turboSMTP's compliance with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”) and other applicable privacy legislation.

### Identifying Purposes

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

If you choose to register to become a member of our Site, the Site's registration form requires you to provide personal information, such as your contact information (like name, email address, postal code) and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

If you choose to purchase services from us, we require financial information, such as: a billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. We use this financial information, to verify the accuracy of your name, address, and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our services. We will also use credit card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us, and that the card has not been reported as lost or stolen. We may contact you, as necessary, during the processing of your order for services offered from the Site. We may also use your contact information to contact you when necessary, for example, to respond to your comments or requests for information, to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems, as permitted by law.

If you choose to post messages in message areas or leave feedback for us, we will collect that information.

### Consent

Your knowledge and consent are required for our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. When you visit the Site, we may ask you for personal information. It is your choice whether or not you submit personal information to us.  Generally, when you voluntarily provide us with your personal information, we will assume you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of that information for the purposes identified at the time of collection.

Sometimes we will seek your express consent. For example, to become a member of the Site, we may ask if you want to register for e-mail distribution or other services using an “opt-in” mechanism. You will not receive communications or services from us unless you click the box expressing your express consent.

### Withdrawal of Consent

If, at any time, you decide you do not wish to receive communications from us or you no longer wish to receive our services, you can let us know by contacting us using the Contact Information below.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a turboSMTP member if you return to the turboSMTP site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to your turboSMTP account by entering your e-mail address and password. These cookies allow us to identify you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don't need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect.

We also use longer-lasting cookies to recognize you as our member or to process your account’s registration. If the account’s registration was not completed the cookies are stored for 30 days only. Otherwise, when the account registration was completed the cookies are stored to allow you to enter your email, password and some other options less frequently during a session. turb SMTP uses cookies to provide information that is targeted to your interests, offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookies.

You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

### Limiting Collection, Use and Disclosure

 **Use**

turboSMTP does not use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than those identified at the time of collection.  If we want to use your personal information for purposes not identified at that time, we will obtain your consent, unless use of your personal information for the new purpose is required by law.

 **Disclosure**

turboSMTP will not disclose your personal information to third parties except in the limited circumstances described below, or with your express consent. These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is disclosed.

  1. Agent and Contractors. We share information with companies that we hire to help us perform certain services, such as technical support and financial institutions processing any payments.
  2. Permitted or Required by Law. Applicable privacy laws in US permit or require the disclosure of personal information without consent in limited circumstances. Where permitted or required by applicable laws, we may disclose your personal information. For example, we may disclose your personal information in response to a subpoena, warrant, or court order.
  3. Breach of the User Agreement. We may also disclose personal information that we in good faith believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our User Agreement. For example, this means that if we conduct a fraud investigation and conclude that one side has engaged in deceptive practices, we can give that person or entity's contact information (but not bank account or credit card information) to victims who request it.

 **Retention**

We retain your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill identified purposes, unless a longer retention is permitted or required by law.

 **Accuracy**

Information that you provide to turboSMTP must be true, accurate and complete. We rely on you to inform us of any changes in your personal information (contact details, address, telephone number or email address) by updating them using the online Control Panel or by contacting us using the Contact Information below.

 **Safeguards**

turboSMTP uses physical, administrative and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access and disclosure.  For example, we use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as credit card payment information.

Your credit card information is stored only in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. We test our security systems regularly and also contract with outside companies to audit our security systems and processes.  
If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account at https://turbo-smtp.com and contact us right away as described below.

 **Access to Information**

You have a right to request access to, and to challenge the accuracy and completeness of, your personal information. You also have a right to receive a general accounting of how that information has been used and disclosed, subject to certain circumstances prescribed by law.

To request access to, or to amend, your personal information, please contact us in writing using the Contact Information below.  We may need to verify your identity before responding to your request.

 **Challenging Compliance**

turboSMTP has procedures in place to receive and respond to inquiries about its policies and practices relating to its handling of personal information. Inquiries should be directed to turboSMTP's Privacy Officer, using the Contact Information below.  We will take appropriate measures to resolve it, including, if necessary, amending this Statement and its procedures.

turboSMTP will investigate all complaints and will respond within 30 days of receipt of a written inquiry.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments or complaints about this Policy or our handling of your personal information, or if you wish to withdraw your consent to our use of your personal information or to request access to or update any information we have on file, please contact our Privacy Officer using the contact information below:

TURBO SMTP CORP.  
545 East 14 St. #mf  
New York, NY 10009  
Email to: privacy@turbo-smtp.com
